Sibasish Dey

17 Chandra Mondal lane • Kolkata, West Bengal 700 026 • deysibasish55@gmail.com • 8981163350

SUMMARY

I am working as a Web Designer with 8 years of experience in managing multiple websites and web application design projects. Adept at developing creative and functional UX/UI designs, web page layouts and infrastructure to maintain a cohesive website consistent with clients' specific requirements and also gathering knowledge in User Experience.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, RWD, Bootstrap Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop

PORTFOLIO LINK

https://sibasishdey.github.io/project_pocketLib/

EXPERIENCE

Mapps IT Services Pvt Ltd Web Designer

Kolkata, West Bengal March 2021 - Present

Role and Responsibilities

- Design email templates and purl web templates
- I make responsive email templates and purl websites (personalized microsites) by using HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap.
- Collaborated with my project manager and developer team and complete within deadline.

Cognizant Technology Solutions India Private Ltd Associate

Kolkata, West Bengal January 2016 – July 2020

Project: Group R-Responsive Web & Search

Project: Service 360 UI-UX Assessment

Project: PH Franchisee Dashboard.

Role and Responsibilities

- Making html pages according to VD
- Giving supports to programmer in development phase.
- Solving responsive issues in different view port.

Project description

Client's current website was only for desktop version so they want to change into responsive design as per the current trend and for access from mobile and table.

Role and Responsibilities

Making a POC for client so they can understand how the application works

Project description

From onsite manager and my Senior Consultant have make some wireframes as per the clients requirement. Over webex Senior Consultant told me for making a interactive wireframes for the can show to the clicent how the application going to work. So they give me 2 weeks deadline to finish the interactive wireframes. I committed to them and finish the POC. After complete that they send us some changes and I make those changes in interactive wireframes and uploaded in sharepoint.

Role and Responsibilities

• Making the apps UI as per the client's requirement Using and Bootstrap.

Page **1** of **2**

Sibasish Dey

17 Chandra Mondal lane • Kolkata, West Bengal 700 026 • deysibasish55@gmail.com • 8981163350

- Taking care of code refactoring (HTML, CSS &LESS).
- Responsive Testing.
- Defect fixing.

Project description

In this project I have done some UI model in Bootstrap like: Table , progress bar , buttons .Also creates some responsive html pages, using Bootstrap and LESS.

Role and Responsibilities:

- Project: Innovation app Family Dollar (FD) Account
- Doing PSD Conversation using Bootstrap.
- Build a responsive UI for iPhone, iPad and desktop.

Brainium information technologies pvt. Ltd Web Designer

Kolkata, West Bengal Feb 2013 - Jan 2016

Role and Responsibilities

- Making RWD Website with Cross-Browser Compatibility.
- Give design support in projects.
- Working with developer team and complete within deadline

EDUCATION

Rabindra bharati university, Kolkata _{M.A}

Kolkata, West Bengal Passing Year 2012